Sciurls Privacy Policy
======================

Last updated: 2018-12-06

Browserling Inc ("us", "we", or "our") URLs and Browserling Services provided on or through mobile applications, websites, third party platforms including social networking sites or similar communication platforms that you have linked with our applications and websites ("Third Party Platforms"), and various API Services and other Services that we may offer from time to time (collectively, the "Services").

This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information when you use our Services.

We use your Personal Information for providing and improving the Services. By using the Services, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, accessible at sciurls.com.

Information Collection And Use
------------------------------

While using our Services, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you. Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to, your email address, name, phone number, postal address ("Personal Information").

We collect this information for the purpose of providing the Services, identifying and communicating with you, responding to your requests/inquiries, servicing your purchase orders, and improving our Services.

Log Data
--------

We collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Services ("Log Data"). This Log Data may include information such as your computer's Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser type, browser version, the pages of our Services that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages and other statistics.

In addition, we may use third party services, such as Google Analytics and Statcounter, that collect, monitor and analyze this type of information in order to increase our Services's functionality. These third party service providers have their own privacy policies addressing how they use such information.

Cookies
-------

Cookies are files with a small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a web site and transferred to your device. We use cookies to collect information in order to improve our Services for you.

You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. The Help feature on most browsers provide information on how to accept cookies, disable cookies or to notify you when receiving a new cookie.

If you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some features of our Services and we recommend that you leave them turned on.

Do Not Track Disclosure
-----------------------

We do not support Do Not Track ("DNT"). Do Not Track is a preference you can set in your web browser to inform websites that you do not want to be tracked.

You can enable or disable Do Not Track by visiting the Preferences or Settings page of your web browser.

Services Providers
------------------

We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Services, to provide the Services on our behalf, to perform Services-related Services and/or to assist us in analyzing how our Services are used.

These third parties have access to your Personal Information only to perform specific tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use your information for any other purpose.

Browserling may take your Personal Information and make it non-personally identifiable, either by combining it with information about other individuals (aggregating your information with information about other individuals), or by removing characteristics (such as your name) that make the information personally identifiable to you (de-personalizing your information). Given the nature of this information, there are no restrictions under this Privacy Policy upon the right of Browserling to aggregate or de-personalize your personal information, and Browserling may use and/or share with third parties the resulting non-personally identifiable information in any manner in Browserling's sole discretion.

Communications
--------------

We may use your Personal Information to contact you with newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information that may be of interest to you. You may opt out of receiving any, or all, of these communications from us by following the unsubscribe link or instructions provided in any email we send or by contacting us.

Compliance With Laws
--------------------

Browserling may also disclose and/or transfer your Personal Information: (1) in response to judicial or governmental subpoenas, warrants, or orders served on or delivered to Browserling; (2) if needed, as determined in Browserling's sole discretion, to protect Browserling's rights or property, to enforce the provisions of this Privacy Policy and/or Browserling's Terms of Service, and/or to prevent harm to yourself or others; and (3) if Browserling files a petition for relief is filed under U.S. Bankruptcy laws for or against Browserling, or if Browserling becomes subject to an order of appointment of a trustee or receiver.

Business Transaction
--------------------

If Browserling is involved in a merger, acquisition or asset sale, your Personal Information may be transferred as a business asset. In such cases, we will provide notice before your Personal Information is transferred and/or becomes subject to a different Privacy Policy.

Security
--------

The security of your Personal Information is important to us, and we strive to implement and maintain reasonable, commercially acceptable security procedures and practices appropriate to the nature of the information we store, in order to protect it from unauthorized access, destruction, use, modification, or disclosure.

However, please be aware that no method of transmission over the internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure and we are unable to guarantee the absolute security of the Personal Information we have collected from you.

International Transfer
----------------------

Your information, including Personal Information, may be transferred to - and maintained on - computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection laws may differ than those from your jurisdiction.

If you are located outside United States and choose to provide information to us, please note that we transfer the information, including Personal Information, to United States and process it there.

Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.

Links To Other Sites
--------------------

Our Services may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party's site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit.

We have no control over, and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services.

Children's Privacy
------------------

Only persons age 18 or older have permission to access our Services. Our Services does not address anyone under the age of 13 ("Children").

We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13. If you are a parent or guardian and you learn that your Children have provided us with Personal Information, please contact us. If we become aware that we have collected Personal Information from a children under age 13 without verification of parental consent, we take steps to remove that information from our servers.

Changes To This Privacy Policy
------------------------------

This Privacy Policy is effective as of 2018-12-06 and will remain in effect except with respect to any changes in its provisions in the future, which will be in effect immediately after being posted on this page.

We reserve the right to update or change our Privacy Policy at any time and you should check this Privacy Policy periodically. Your continued use of the Services after we post any modifications to the Privacy Policy on this page will constitute your acknowledgment of the modifications and your consent to abide and be bound by the modified Privacy Policy.

If we make any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you either through the email address you have provided us, or by placing a prominent notice on our website.

Contact Us
----------

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us.
